The 1st Kawana Lake
Yay!
Hello everyone!
We
Natakarumi here.
This is our annual big event.
This time, we'd like to decide who knows the most about NARUKARUMI.
I'd like to choose the member who knows the most about NARUKARUMI!
Yay!
We've been working on this big project for a while now.
I'll summarize the result...
Okay, so...
Honma is Moe, Nakata is Miru, Suganami and Suzuki are Ogi, Kawaguchi is Mouken, Tomita is Saya, Tanizaki is Chi-san, and Kochia and Ogi are Hi-chan!
Oh!
I'll look for them.
No, oh, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey...
It's like you tried to leave it for us.
That's right!
Thanks!
I'm pretty sure we have a lot of confidence.
I have a lot of confidence.
I'm pretty excited about it.
I'm putting it in here and the person who was chosen was chosen.
I'd like to have it. So let's get right to it to see who will be the river name issue.
Now here is the first question.
Who will be the next Dokashi?
Can you guess?
Hirah.
I gave you three.
Three?
So one of them is a winner?
I guess I'll take that as a yes.
One for each.
Three points tops.
Certainly the best.
Here we go.
Oh!
Did you write it?
Yes, sir.
Okay, everyone open your answers!
Yes!
Rice crackers, potato chips, and jagarico.
What about you, Ogi-chan?
Kamayaki
I'm wearing two Umaibo!
You're hanging out with Kamayaki and Umaibo today, too!
That's it!
I don't know your magazine.
No, it's candy.
Why bother with magazines?
How could I not know?
Okay, here's the correct answer.
Don't be lazy. It's Nerner Nerner Nerner and Crackle Panic.
That's good!
You hit it on purpose!
You bought the money!
That's great!
I wonder if Momochan gets a point?
One point?
One point!
Is it okay?
I'm so happy.
Now, let's go to the second question.
Here is the second question!
Which member left the biggest impression on you when you first met?
If I write down someone, will I win?
There was a girl who left quite an impression on me when I first met her.
But you know what, I've never mentioned it.
Well, no, it's probably not one of ours.
I'm sure it's not one of ours.
Not at the audition.
Ehhhh...
Potential.
Yeah, well, good luck smiling.
Wait a minute... that's not Ames.
So you got it?
Yes, sir.
Then I'd like to open the floor to everyone's answers.
I thought it was Nacchan, but everyone's talking about Nacchan.
I thought it was Nacchan... but everyone said "Nacchan" at first, so I thought it wasn't.
I saw "Milten" at the beginning and thought it was Milten.
I told you about Milten earlier. The reason is... when I first saw him, I thought he was a cool kid.
I didn't talk to her directly at the time, so I thought she had a pretty face and was cool, but when I talked to her she said she was cute.
I see.
I might have heard that before.
They were all right.
It's a shame.
Well, that was a little close.
I'm so frustrated, so I'd like to move on to the third question.
Okay, here is the third question.
If you could use only one magic, what kind of magic would you want to learn?
I think I have confidence in this one.
I can put myself in Natsumi's mind and think about it, can't I?
But I've said this a lot.
Is that so?
Is that so? It's important if you put yourself in our mind.
You two should be.
I'm working on it.
Let's open it up! Ready!
Boom!
I want to go home soon,
I want to be a cat.
I want to be a cat, and I want to be able to use the Nyannyan language.
So you want to talk like a cat.
That's for sure.
Yes, that's right. Then, here is the correct answer. Manipulation of time.
I've never heard of it. What do you mean by "manipulate time"? There is not enough time, right?
So I want to stop or increase it. I see.
So, no one won. I was pretty confident.
Now, here is the fourth question. Please strike a pose.
What pose?
Se-no!
Cute!
Now, here is the correct answer.
This way!
I was lost.
This one was right, though.
So no one got it right.
It was frustrating.
Next, the fifth question.
Only I throw it away.
Eel's cute side is a little bit and a little bit.
I'm lost, because there are so many.
Only I am dead, right?
The point is that only Natsumi is dead.
But I'm aware that I chose her because I know her.
Yes, yes, yes.
She's so confident.
If not me, who's going to challenge him first?
Sorry, sorry.
Please give me a hint
The room is quite...
Oh, my God.
What's that?
Is that what it looks like?
We share a lot of rooms, don't we? Like when you sleep over.
Well, let me just show you... now.
Oh, really?
I'm just saying he's cute.
You're in love with her.
Doesn't that happen often?
Not really.
It's just normal, you know?
I'd know if I made her pretty.
I'm glad you think it's nice.
I'd like to have a nosey talk with you first, Mr. Ogi.
Everything you have is frilly pink.
He says he sings all the time. He sings it all the time.
Okay, please answer my question about the toys.
Jan, I've been closed since I woke up from sleep....
Oh!
I'm a pretty good sleeper.
I see.
I'll try to go back to sleep when I wake up.
Huh?
Let's take a look.
Here's your answer.
Doh-doh! Doh-doh!
I often sleep in the same room with you.
I have to stop the alarm several times when I wake up in the morning.
You're not a good sleeper, are you?
You shouldn't lie.
In a way.
In a way, it's like...
Like waking up from sleep.
It's the closest thing I can think of.
You lied.
It takes me a while to wake up.
I just meant that it takes me a while to wake up, but when I do, I feel refreshed.
Is that cute?
It's cute.
You're cute.
You should go home. You're sleepy.
You're trying to stop me.
Yeah, you're right, it's kind of cute.
No?
What do you think?
Seven seventy-five.
7.75?
What?
It's higher than the first one, too.
I made a mistake.
0.75?
It was 0.75.
Early in the morning, 0.75.
0.75 points.
Well, I'm very happy.
The other way around.......
Hime-chan
Oh no, only Momoki-kun got points now.
It stopped.
I'll move on to the next one.
Question 6.
Dong! Tomorrow is my first date with Mr. Suganami.
Where do you want to go? What do you want to do?
What are you going to do?
Off all day?
Not much.
I hadn't really thought about it. I'm just trying to pinpoint the big place.
What? I don't know. I don't know, just write it down.
What is it?
Natsumi, you can't be a roller coaster.
It's different if you don't tell me. It's not?
I'll get mad if you don't tell me.
Are you done?
Okay, let's hear from Momochan and Ouchi-chan.
Let's see what you've got.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Oh, great!
A game at home!
Oh, my gosh!
At your house, Ray.
I don't know, here, doesn't he seem like he'd say he wants to go home?
And she seems like she likes games.
You seem like you like games. I could see that.
May I?
Which one?
I'm going to the Ib Neko Cafe.
I see.
That sounds like a possibility.
Natsumi's answer, please.
Yes, that's right. A movie.
Amusement parks are also nice.
Anywhere is fun with Mirelei.
Where would you like to go?
Okay, I'll do this.
Wait.
I want to make an announcement.
Kinerene is always early for everything.
Yes!
So...
What a lucky problem for us!
That's one point for me.
Next time, make it about 5 next time.
75 points.
Last point?
Really?
Now, question 7.
The way you set Ogi-san up by becoming his mother.
I don't have an image of her being angry with me, so I thought that's what it would be like if she was angry with me.
So, I should write about how Hana is always angry with me?
That's another 75 points.
Yes, yes, yes.
Hana, because all you have to do is write what your mom tells you. Okay, I'll start with Momochan and my answer.
Hey, what are you doing watching cartoons? Hey, that's a child... get a grip!
Oko, oko, you're mad. You're mad. Then why don't you tell Saruma that you're a mom and a girl?
I don't understand. What about you, Oki-chan? Okay, MomoMono?
No, no, no, no, uh, I want to be a mom.
Listen, listen. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I want 75.
Okay, let's see the answers.
Don?
Flowers?
Buckwheat.
Hana?
Yes.
Wow.
What?
Oh, my God.
This is a little... What do we do with this?
What is this?
What do we do?
Natsumi, minus 70.
What's that?
It's a flower.
Can you write "flower"?
I wonder if it was good... if anyone wrote it.
Bingo!
No, maybe not.
Not even close.
Not at all.
So, let me get my points straight.
First, Momo-chan has 1.75 points
And Ugi-chan has 0 points
And I have 1 point
Kawanago is now Momo Kyun!
I'm so happy!
Congratulations!
Thank you!
If I didn't have a lucky problem, I would have 0 points.
What's your lucky problem?
Well, I'll make one next time.
I'll give you a second try, right?
That's all for now, I'm Kawanago!
Bye bye!
It was fun!